- [Bun B] I might put away, to put it,
give you the mustache.
(helicopter whirs)
I ain't a player, I just crush a lot.
I'm not a player, I just crush a lot.
(beeping)
(piano playing)
♪ (T.S.) Don't wanna be a player ♪
♪ I don't wanna be a playa no more ♪
♪ I'm not a playa I just crush a lot ♪
♪ But Big Punisher, still
got what you're lookin' for ♪
♪ For my thugs ♪
Don't wanna be, don't wanna be
♪ I don't wanna be a playa no more ♪
♪ I'm not a playa I just crush a lot ♪
♪ But you know Big Punisher
still down by law ♪
♪ Who's down to crush a lot ♪
♪ Hey yo, I'm still not a
player but you still a hater ♪
♪ Elevator to the top hah,
see you later, I'm gone ♪
♪ Penthouse suite, Penthouse freaks ♪
♪ In house beach, French
countess, ten thou piece ♪
♪ Rent-out lease, with a option to buy ♪
♪ Coppin' a five-oh Benz for
when I'm not, far up in the sky ♪
♪ From my Twinzito ♪
♪ Up in the Benzito with my kiko ♪
♪ From Queens, nicknamed Perico ♪
♪ We go back like PA's and wearing PJ's ♪
♪ Now we reach the
peak-age, for three days ♪
♪ Who wanna ride? It
won't cost you a dollar ♪
♪ Whether soft or harder of
course you still gonna holla ♪
♪ Momma, I'm big, I rip my through your ♪
♪ I'm sick, you couldn't
measure my with six rulers ♪
♪ Hold up, chula, I'm
all about getting' loot ♪
♪ But I knock that boot,
if you out to get HOOF ♪
♪ I don't wanna be a playa no more ♪
♪ I'm not a playa I just
crush a lot (No more) ♪
♪ But Big Punisher, still
got what you're lookin' for ♪
♪ Uptown baby, uptown ♪
♪ I don't wanna be a playa no more ♪
♪ I'm not a playa I just crush a lot ♪
♪ But you know Big Punisher
still down by law ♪
♪ Who's down to crush tonight ♪
♪ I love from butter pecan
to blackberry molasses ♪
♪ I don't discriminate, I
regulate every shade of that ♪
♪ Long as you show
class, and pass my test ♪
♪ Fat, highly intelligent bachelorettes ♪
♪ That's the best, I
won't settle for less ♪
♪ I wanna ghetto brunette,
with unforgettable ♪
♪ I lay your head on my chest,
come feel my heartbeat ♪
♪ We can park the Jeep,
pump Mobb Deep and just ♪
♪ It's hard to creep since I found Joe ♪
♪ Every pretty round
brown wanna go down low ♪
♪ But this Boogie Down
professional, I'm let you know ♪
♪ Once I put the blows,
get your clothes, ♪
♪ 'cause you got to go ♪
♪ I could go downstairs,
little brown everywhere ♪
♪ "You nasty Twin!" ♪
♪ I don't care ♪
♪ Round here they call me Big
Pun, if you with the big ♪
♪ Thick tongue, known to make a chick ♪
♪ (In the) hot tub, popping bubbly ♪
♪ Rubbing your spot love, got
you screamin' "Punish me" ♪
♪ But it don't stop,
watch the Pun get wicked ♪
♪ When I even Luke be like
"Don't stop, get it get it" ♪
♪ Up in the hot tub, poppin' bubbly ♪
♪ Rubbing your spot love, got
you screaming "Punish me" ♪
♪ But it don't stop,
watch the Pun get wicked ♪
♪ When I even Luke be like
"Don't stop, get it get it" ♪
♪ I don't wanna be a playa no more ♪
♪ [Background] Punisher,
Punisher, Punisher, Big Punisher ♪
♪ But Big Punisher, still
got what you're lookin' for ♪
♪ Punisher, ooh, Big Punisher ♪
♪ I don't wanna be a playa no more ♪
♪ Punisher, Punisher,
Punisher, Big Punisher ♪
♪ But you know Big Punisher
still down by law ♪
♪ Punisher, ooh, Big Punisher ♪
♪ Who's down to crush a lot ♪
♪ Boricua, morena, boricua, morena ♪
♪ No more rollin' with an entourage ♪
♪ Unless it's Pun and the Terror Squad ♪
♪ Punisher, Punisher,
Punisher, Big Punisher ♪
♪ Punisher... Joe and Big Punisher ♪
♪ Boricua, morena, boricua, morena ♪